JACKSON DAVIS

jacksonmdavis@gmail.com | +1 406-260-1005 | sevenhillsmt.com/jackson-portfolio

OBJECTIVE

Versatile, reliable professional with a breadth of experience seeks to launch lifelong career in Al/Machine Learning. Strong soft skills foundation, excellent communication ability, fluent in English and Mandarin. Currently enrolled in Artificial Intelligence M.S. program at Johns Hopkins University. Recent projects include work in image processing/computer vision and NLP, currently pursuing guided independent research in organic language emergence in multi-agent RL environments.

SKILLS

- Python (Advanced) and C++ (Intermediate)
- Pandas, Numpy, Scipy, Sklearn, Jupyter, etc.
- Some Pytorch/Keras/Tensorflow + CUDA
- Data preprocessing and basic visualization

- Abundant soft skills training and experience
- Microsoft Office (Excel/Word/Etc.), CMS Web Design
- Pro Tools, Logic Pro, et al. (Audio production)
- Chief Architect, Lumion et al. (CAD/Architecture)

EDUCATION

JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY | Baltimore, MD (Remote)

MS - Artificial Intelligence | January 2023 - Current | GPA: 4.0

- Coursework in Algorithms/Data Structures, Search/planning, Optimization and Machine Learning
- Also completed bachelor-level coursework in Statistics, Linear Algebra, Python and C++

UNIVERSITY OF FLORIDA | Gainesville, FL

BA - Linguistics | August 2004 – August 2008 | GPA: 3.11

• National Merit Scholar, Bright Futures Scholar

EXPERIENCE

Research Assistant | Yasin Research Group | Durham NC, USA (remote) | May 2024 - Current

Currently conducting guided independent research on language emergence in multi-agent RL environments

Al Language Model Trainer | DataAnnotation | Durham NC, USA (remote) | January 2024 - Current

- Trained language models on coding topics, primarily ML topics in Python, through providing and reviewing code samples, comparing and editing model outputs, and evaluating model performance
- Being a consistently successful trainer requires attention to detail, understanding of a variety of coding topics, and a strong command of the target natural language

Architectural Designer | Seven Hills Construction | Whitefish MT, USA | May 2018 - July 2022

- Self-taught architectural, structural, drafting, and CAD techniques to build in-house design studio for General Contractor
- Coordinated with clients and construction team, requiring both clear communication and deep technical knowledge
- Designed large, complex projects often valued at several million dollars; won overall "Best in Class" for county-wide Parade of Homes with second ever design project
- Learned to efficiently multi-task while playing integral role in company's apprx. 400% growth over 4 years

Music Producer | The 7 Music Studio | Suzhou, Jiangsu, China | April 2015 - May 2018

- Recorded and produced a wide variety of music in a professional recording studio
- Concurrently maintained independent music, television, and performance career, including several notable performances and awards (see portfolio)

Marketing/Event Manager | The Bookworm | Suzhou, Jiangsu, China | April 2013 - December 2014

Managed marketing and events operations for a full-service restaurant/bar/performance venue, including large-scale
Music Festival and Literary Festival. Won "Restaurant of the Year" 2014, and doubled revenue within a single year

Spoken English Instructor | Xuchang University | Xuchang, Henan, China | August 2009 - June 2011

Designed curriculum for and taught spoken English courses at a Chinese university

LANGUAGES

• English (Native), Mandarin (Fluent)